Colors(颜色）:

Black ("&0");（黑色）
Dark Blue ("&1");（暗蓝色）
Dark Green ("&2");（暗绿色）
Dark Aqua ("&3");（暗浅绿色）	
Dark Red ("&4");（暗红）
Dark Purple ("&5");（暗紫色）
Gold ("&6");（金色）
Gray ("&7");灰色）
Dark Gray ("&8");（暗灰色）
Blue ("&9");（蓝）
Green ("&a");（绿色）
Aqua ("&b");（浅绿色）
Red ("&c");（红）
Light Purple ("&d");（光紫色）
Yellow ("&e");（黄色）
White ("&f");（白色）

Special:

Obfuscated ("&k");
Bold ("&l");
Strikethrough ("&m");
Underline ("&n");
Italic ("&o");
Reset ("&r");

Configuration (config.yml):

---
#REMEMBER THAT IF YOU USE CustomAlerts EXTENSIONS, MESSAGES MAY NOT FOLLOW THE DEFAULT CONFIG
#Date/Time format (replaced in {TIME}). For format codes read http://php.net/manual/en/datetime.formats.php
datetime-format: "H:i:s"
#Server Motd message settings (available from MCPE 0.11.0 and later)
Motd:
#Motd update timeout
update-timeout: 1
#Show custom Motd
custom: true
#Motd message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&e[{TIME}] &aWelcome to your server! &n&b[{MAXPLAYERS}/{TOTALPLAYERS}]"
#Outdated Client message (available from MCPE 0.11.0 BUILD 11 and later)
OutdatedClient:
#Show custom Outdated Client message
custom: true
#Outdated Client message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&cYour MCPE client is outdated!"
#Outdated Server message (available from MCPE 0.11.0 BUILD 11 and later)
OutdatedServer:
#Show custom Outdated Server message
custom: true
#Outdated Server message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&cOops! Server outdated!"
#Whitelisted Server message (available from MCPE 0.11.0 BUILD 11 and later)
WhitelistedServer:
#Show custom Whitelisted Server message
custom: true
#Whitelisted Server message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c&oThis Server is whitelisted!"
#First Join message settings
FirstJoin:
#Enable First Join message
enable: true
#First Join message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&2[{TIME}] &a{PLAYER}&d joined the game for the first time."
#Join message settings
Join:
#Hide Join message
hide: false
#Show custom Join message 
custom: true
#Join message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&2[{TIME}] &a{PLAYER}&e joined the game."
#Quit message settings
Quit:
#Hide Quit message
hide: true
#Show custom Quit message 
custom: false
#Quit message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&4[{TIME}] &c{PLAYER}&e has left the game"
#World Change message settings
WorldChange:
#Enable World Change message
enable: true
#World Change message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {ORIGIN}: Show origin world name
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TARGET}: Show target world name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&2[{TIME}] &a{PLAYER}&e moved from &c{ORIGIN}&e to &a{TARGET}"
#Death message settings
Death:
#Hide deafult Death message
hide: false
#Show custom default Death message
custom: true
#Default Death message
#Available Tags:
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} died"
#Death by contact message
death-contact-message:
#Hide Death by contact message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by contact message
custom: true
#Death by contact message
#Available Tags:
# - {BLOCK}: The name of the block which killed the player
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&cOops! {PLAYER} was killed by {BLOCK}"
#Death by entity message (players and mobs)
kill-message:
#Hide Death by entity message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by entity message
custom: true
#Death by entity message
# - {KILLER}: The name of the killer entity
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&9{PLAYER} &ewas killed by &c{KILLER}"
#Death by projectile message
death-projectile-message:
#Hide Death by projectile message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by projectile message
custom: true
#Death by projectile message
# - {KILLER}: The name of the killer entity
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} was killed by {KILLER} by arrow"
#Death by suffocation message
death-suffocation-message:
#Hide Death by suffocation message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by suffocation message
custom: true
#Death by suffocation message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} suffocated"
#Death by fall message
death-fall-message:
#Hide Death by fall message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by fall message
custom: true
#Death by fall message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} fell from a high place"
#Death by fire message
death-fire-message:
#Hide Death by fire message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by fire message
custom: true
#Death by fire message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} went up in flames"
#Death on fire message
death-on-fire-message:
#Hide Death on fire message
hide: false
#Show custom Death on fire message
custom: true
#Death on fire message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} burned"
#Death by lava message
death-lava-message:
#Hide Death by lava message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by lava message
custom: true
#Death by lava message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} tried to swim in lava"
#Death by drowning message
death-drowning-message:
#Hide Death by drowning message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by drowning message
custom: true
#Death by drowning message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} drowned"
#Death by explosion message
death-explosion-message:
#Hide Death by explosion message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by explosion message
custom: true
#Death by explosion message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} exploded"
#Death by void message
death-void-message:
#Hide Death by void message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by void message
custom: true
#Death by void message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} fell into the void"
#Death by suicide message
death-suicide-message:
#Hide Death by suicide message
hide: false
#Show custom Death by suicide message
custom: true
#Death by suicide message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} committed suicide"
#Death magic message
death-magic-message:
#Hide Death magic message
hide: false
#Show custom Death magic message
custom: true
#Death magic message
# - {MAXPLAYERS}: Show the maximum number of players supported by the server
# - {PLAYER}: Show player name
# - {TIME}: Show current time
# - {TOTALPLAYERS}: Show the number of all online players
message: "&c{PLAYER} was killed by a spell"
...

Commands:

/customalerts - CustomAlerts commands (aliases: [calerts])

Permissions:

- customalerts.* - CustomAlerts permissions.
- customalerts.help - CustomAlerts command Help permission.
- customalerts.info - CustomAlerts command Info permission.
- customalerts.reload - CustomAlerts command Reload permission.
